askwebhosting.com 2013-05-06

# Ask Web Hosting Web Hosting Directory AskWebHosting

**Privacy statement**

We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to askwebhosting.com will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [let us know](mailto:privacy@askwebhosting.com)

 **Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**

We does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists. 

**Browser information collected on the website:**

We analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. 

**Use of cookies:**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. askwebhosting.com uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use our site if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data and do not read personal data from your machine. Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by **Tribal Fusion** and **Fastclick** , our Web advertising partners. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. 

For more information about Tribal Fusion, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please click [here](http://www.tribalfusion.com/www/about/privacy.html). 

For more information about Fastclick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please click [here](http://www.fastclick.com/about/privacy.html). 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by askwebhosting.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
